{
  "tourQuests": 
  [
    {
      "questCount": 16,
      "tourName": "Буквы", 
      "quests": [
        {
          "question": "Найди букву А!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "Б", "К", "Ч" ],
          "right_answer": "А"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву О!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "А", "И", "А" ],
          "right_answer": "О"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву С!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "П", "В", "К" ],
          "right_answer": "С"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву М!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "А", "Ы", "В" ],
          "right_answer": "М"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву В!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "А", "Ы", "О" ],
          "right_answer": "В"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву Н!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "П", "Ы", "М" ],
          "right_answer": "Н"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву П!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "П", "Ы", "М" ],
          "right_answer": "П"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву К!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "Р", "Ы", "Р" ],
          "right_answer": "К"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву А!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "Б", "К", "Ч" ],
          "right_answer": "_А"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву О!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "А", "И", "А" ],
          "right_answer": "_О"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву С!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "П", "В", "К" ],
          "right_answer": "_С"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву М!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "А", "Ы", "В" ],
          "right_answer": "_М"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву В!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "А", "Ы", "О" ],
          "right_answer": "_В"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву Н!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "П", "Ы", "М" ],
          "right_answer": "_Н"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву П!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "П", "Ы", "М" ],
          "right_answer": "_П"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди букву К!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "Р", "Ы", "Р" ],
          "right_answer": "_К"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questCount": 4,
      "tourName": "Слоги",
      "quests": [
        {
          "question": "Найди слог МА!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АВ", "ИМ", "КА" ],
          "right_answer": "МА"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди слог МО!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АВ", "ИМ", "КА" ],
          "right_answer": "МО"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди слог СА!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АВ", "ИМ", "КА" ],
          "right_answer": "СА"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди слог СО!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АВ", "ИМ", "КА" ],
          "right_answer": "СО"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questCount": 4,
      "tourName": "Слова",
      "quests": [
        {
          "question": "Найди слово Мама!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АМ-АМ", "РА-РА", "ЖЕ-ЖЕ" ],
          "right_answer": "МА-МА"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди слово Папа!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АМ-АМ", "РА-РА", "ЖЕ-ЖЕ" ],
          "right_answer": "ПА-ПА"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди слово Мост!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АМ-АМ", "РА-РА", "ЖЕ-ЖЕ" ],
          "right_answer": "МО-СТ"
        },
        {
          "question": "Найди слово Куст!",
          "wrong_answers": [ "АМ-АМ", "РА-РА", "ЖЕ-ЖЕ" ],
          "right_answer": "КУ-СТ"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}